# SHAAKIRAH RIDDER

**PROFILE** 

**PHONE** 078 636 9896

**EMAIL** shaakirahridder@gmail.com **ADDRESS** 

Kuilsriver, Cape Town

Graduate with Bachelor of Social Science in Psychology and Social Development, currently completing Honours in Social Development at the University of Cape Town. Interested in HR, Recruitment, Social Media, Reception, Learning and Development, Administration, work experience.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Social Science University of Cape Town**

- Psychology and Social Development
- 2020 2024

# **Honours in Social Development University of Cape Town**

- Social Development
- Current: 2024

# **SKILLS**

Strong computer and technology skills Excellent communication skills Data capturing in spreadsheets/ systems Microsoft Office Google Sheets Proficient in admin tasks Strong time management skills Multitasking and Deadline driven

### **LANGUAGES**

English **Afrikaans** 

# **REFERENCES**

#### TRACEY SCHOLTZ

**BIJOUX LUCY / HR** 

Email: scholtztracey@gmail.com

#### WHITNEY ABRAHAMS

MANGO 5 / HR

Phone: +27 78 712 9799

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **PERSONAL ASSISTANT REVIVE MARKETING**

2020 - 2021

- Make travel arrangements, scheduling appointments
- Maintain database and filing system using Excel
- Assist with company events and social media content
- Take notes during meetings, deal with emails and letters
- Answering/making phone calls, calendar management

# CUSTOMER SERVICE ADVISOR

2021 - 2022

**CAPITA** 

- · Handle incoming calls, chats and emails
- Provide customer service experience, resolve queries
- Complete payments and account manager
- Data entry and validation through specific processes

# **ASSISTANT TO OWNER**

2022 - 2023

- **BIJOUX LUCY**
- Manage spreadsheets, update records
- Provide customer service experience, resolve queries
- Interview and assess prospective applicants
- Calendar management, schedule meetings.
- Social media management and marketing

# **VERIFICATION SPECIALIST**

2022 - 2023

#### MANGO 5

- Reach out to company representatives to obtain information
- Complete verifications within time frame.
- Build relationships through phone, email, chat, online forms
- Handle sensitive personal data inline with security policies
- Multi-task and manoeuvre through different systems